Guide to the Indivisible: Stories of American Community Records, 1999-2002 RL.10139
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Indivisible: Stories of American Community records, 1999-2002
1988-2002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Rankin, Tom
Duke University. Center for Documentary Studies
Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University)
Stack, Trudi Wilner
University of Arizona. Center for Creative Photography
RL.10139
14.2 Linear Feet 7250 items
67 Megabytes
The records of the documentary project Indivisible: Stories of American Community span the dates 1988-2002. Through documentary photographs and oral histories, project records, videos, and other materials, the collection documents the social conditions in twelve American communities as well as the history of the project, which explored civil activism, struggle, and change in the following locations: the North Pacific Coast of Alaska; Ithaca, N.Y.; San Francisco, California; Navajo Nation, Arizona and New Mexico; Eau Claire, South Carolina; Delray Beach, Florida; Western North Carolina; Stony Brook, N.Y.; San Juan, Texas; Chicago, Illinois; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania; and the Yaak Valley, Montana. The photographers are Dawoud Bey, Bill Burke, Debbie Fleming Caffery, Lucy Capehart, Lynn Davis, Terry Evans, Lauren Greenfield, Joan Liftin, Reagan Louie, Danny Lyon, Sylvia Plachy, and Eli Reed. The project was sponsored by the Center for Documentary Studies of Duke University and the Center for Creative Photography at the University of Arizona, and co-directed by Tom Rankin and Trudi Stack. Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Historical Note
The Center for Documentary Studies at Duke University was established for the study of the documentary process. "Indivisible: Stories of American Community" was a national documentary project which took place primarily during 1999-2001, and was sponsored by the Center for Documentary Studies in partnership with the Center for Creative Photography at the University of Arizona. The project captured the experiences of individuals participating in grassroots community organizations and activism in twelve American communities at the end of the 20th century.
Collection Overview
The records of the documentary project "Indivisible: Stories of American Community" span the dates 1988-2002, with the bulk of the collection dating from 1999 to 2002, the primary timeframe for the project. Through documentary photographs and oral histories, project records, videos, and other materials, the collection documents the social conditions in twelve American communities as well as the history of the project, which explored civil activism, struggle, and change in the following locations: the North Pacific Coast of Alaska; Ithaca, N.Y.; San Francisco, California; Navajo Nation, Arizona and New Mexico; Eau Claire, South Carolina; Delray Beach, Florida; Western North Carolina; Stony Brook, N.Y.; San Juan, Texas; Chicago, Illinois; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania; and the Yaak Valley, Montana. Each project is fully described in its entry in this collection guide. The project co-directors were Tom Rankin of the Center for Documentary Studies and Trudy Wilner Stack of the Center for Creative Photography. The project was also supported by the Pew Charitable Trusts, the NEA, and other agencies.
The photographs in this collection, most of which formed part of a traveling exhibit, were taken chiefly during 1999 by twelve well-known documentary and landscape photographers working in partnership with project oral history interviewers. The photographers are Dawoud Bey, Bill Burke, Debbie Fleming Caffery, Lucy Capehart, Lynn Davis, Terry Evans, Lauren Greenfield, Joan Liftin, Reagan Louie, Danny Lyon, Sylvia Plachy, and Eli Reed. Their images capture the experiences of individuals participating in grassroots initiatives addressing American social issues such as housing, immigration (in particular, Haitians in Florida), the natural environment, race relations, youth empowerment, and economic and cultural development, and others.
Also preserved in this collection are detailed oral histories recorded in each community, with audio recordings and transcriptions; information on the traveling exhibit; and materials on other project outcomes, including a hardbound large-format book of the images, a postcard exhibit, a guide for educators, booklets and other publications on community organizing, and radio and television programs. Other files document the establishment of research archives based on the documentary project's output, at Duke, in Arizona, and in each of the twelve communities.
The collection is arranged into three series: Audiovisual Resources, Photographs, and Project Files. Audiovisual Resources houses the interview tapes as well as other media associated with the project; Photographs includes photographic prints, most of which accompanied the project book and exhibition; Project Files houses the interview records as well as tape lists, logs, and transcripts in both paper and digital formats. Additional supporting materials found in the Project Files Series include postcards and videocassette tapes from exhibits; a CD-ROM of the 2001 website; field notes in paper and digital format; and other office files generated by the project and its staff, including Tom Rankin, one of the project co-directors.
Acquired as part of the Archives for Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Provenance
The "Indivisible: Stories of American Community" photographs and project records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library in 2002,2006, 2008, and 2011.
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted. Images and recorded interviews may be used for non-commercial, public service, or educational purposes. All other requests to copy, reprint, or republish recorded interviews or printed materials must be made in writing to the Center for Documentary Studies. Researchers who wish to use an interview that does not have a release agreement must read and sign a "Research Agreement for Restricted Materials." All quotes must be taken directly from the recorded interviews, not the printed transcripts or logs.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Also, some of the materials in this collection are not immediately accessible, because they require further processing before use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Conditions Governing Access
Access note. Some materials in this collection are electronic records that require special equipment. Contact Research Services with questions.
San Francisco (Calif.) -- Social conditions -- 1980-; Philadelphia (Pa.) -- Social conditions -- 1980-; Pacific Coast (Alaska) -- Social conditions -- 1980-; North Carolina, Western -- Social conditions -- 1980-; Oral history -- United States; Social problems -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Community life -- United States -- Photographs; Community organization -- United States; Community development -- United States; Chicago (Ill.) -- Social conditions; Delray Beach (Fla.) -- Social conditions -- 1980-; Eau Claire (S.C.) -- Social conditions -- 1980-; Ithaca (N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 1980-; Navajo Nation, Arizona, New Mexico & Utah -- Social conditions -- 1980-; Videocassettes; CD-ROMs; Photographs; Machine-readable records; Transparencies; United States -- Social conditions -- 1980-; Yaak Valley (Mont.) -- Social conditions -- 1980-; Oral histories (document genre); Stony Brook (N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 1980-; San Juan (Tex.) -- Social conditions -- 1980-; Audiovisual materials; Audiocassettes; Voluntarism -- United States; Digital audio tapes; Burke, Bill; Caffery, Debbie Fleming; Davis, Lynn; Evans, Terry; Rankin, Tom; Bey, Dawoud; Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University); Stack, Trudi Wilner; University of Arizona. Center for Creative Photography; Reed, Eli; Plachy, Sylvia; Lyon, Danny; Louie, Reagan; Liftin, Joan; Greenfield, Lauren
- Interviews and related audiovisual resources, 1999-2001; 7 boxes
  Scope and Contents
  The Interviews and Related Audiovisual Resources series includes Interview Recordings, primarily oral history recordings on standard audiocassettes and digital audio tapes, and Associated Media, which contains VHS videocassettes promoting Indivisible. Electronic transcripts for many of the oral histories are available. Contact the Rubenstein Library for further information.
  - Community recordings, 1999-2000; 1
    - Alaska Fishing Communities, North Pacific Coast, AK, 1999-2000; 1; 58 items
      Fifty-eight standard audiocassettes documenting a collaborative project led by the Alaska Marine Conservation Council, to protect and restore marine habitat.
      - Alaska Marine Conservation Council Board Meeting, 3/27/99, Anchorage, AK, 1, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 March 27 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0031)
      - Alaska Marine Conservation Council Board Meeting, 3/27/99, Anchorage, AK. The portion of this tape after Al Tyler (until I say so) is confidential. 2, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 March 27 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0032)
      - Alaska Marine Conservation Council Board Meeting, 3/27-28/99, Anchorage, AK, 3, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 March 27-28 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0033)
      - Alaska Marine Conservation Council Board Meeting, 3/28/99, Anchorage, AK, 4, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 March 28 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0034)
      - AK Marine Conservation Council Board Meeting,, 3/29/99, Anchorage, AK, 5, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 March 29 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0035)
      - Tony Azuyak, Old Harbor, Kodiak, AK, 5/26/99, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 May 26 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0025)
      - Jeff Peterson, Old Harbor, AK, 5/27/99, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 May 27 (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0081)
      - Memorial Service for Fishermen Lost at Sea, Kodiak, AK, May 30, 1999, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 May 30 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0039)
      - Party @ Brian Johnson and Kristin Stahl-Johnson's, Kodiak, AK, 5/30-31/99, Present: B.J., K.S-J., Chuck McWethy, Elinor Poll Ramus, Percy Stihl, Peter C?, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 May 30-31 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0053)
      - [Russian Orthodox] Blessing of the Fleet, Crab Festival, Kodiak, AK, 5/31/99, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 May 31 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0037)
      - Charter Boat fishing trip in Sitka Sound with Eric Jordan, Floyd Tomkins, Brian McNitt, 6/2/99, original standard audio-cassette, 1999 June 02 (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0048)
      - Ted Borbridge, Sitka, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0016)
      - Nevette Bowen, AMCC Board-member, commercial fisher, Yakutat, AK (Side A); Bob Mikol, AMCC Board-member, commercial fisher, fisheries scientist, writer, Fairbanks, AK (Side B), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0017)
      - Phyllis Clough, Old Harbor, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0018)
      - Page Else, Sitka, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0019)
      - Duncan Fields, Kodiak, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0020)
      - Leslie Fields, Kodiak, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0021)
      - Steve Fish, Sitka, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0022)
      - AK Fishing - Alutiiq Dancers Performance @ Alutiiq Museum, Kodiak, AK (J. Lund), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0023)
      - Nick Galaktionoff, Unalaska, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0024)
      - Stosh Anderson, Kodiak, AK, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0026)
      - Theo Grutter, Sitka, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0027)
      - Ralph Guthrie, Sitka, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0028)
      - Pete Hendrickson, Unalaska, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0029)
      - Oliver & Eva Holm, Kodiak (1 of 2), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0030)
      - Kodiak Alutiiq Dancers Performance at Alutiiq Museum in Kodiak, AK, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0036)
      - Kodiak Crab Festival Parade, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0038)
      - Bill Foster, Sitka, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0040)
      - Francine Bennis, AMCC Project Coordinator (staff), Anchorage, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0041)
      - Mary Jo McNally, Sitka, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0042)
      - Ben & Suzi Golodoff, Unalaska, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0043)
      - Wilma Berns & Dave Hilty, Old Harbor, AK, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0044)
      - Chris Berns, Kodiak, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0046)
      - Joe Macinko, Kodiak, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0047)
      - Kristin Stahl-Johnson, Kodiak, (1 of 2), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0049)
      - Kristin Stahl-Johnson, Kodiak, (2 of 2), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0050)
      - Eric Jordan, Sitka, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0051)
      - Brian Johnson, Kodiak, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0052)
      - George "Papa George" Inga, Sr, Old Harbor, Kodiak, AK, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 20, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0054)
      - Oliver Holm, Kodiak (2 of 2), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0075)
      - Jay Skordahl, Sitka, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0076)
      - Carolyn Servid & Dorik Mechau, Sitka, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0077)
      - Julia Suzanne Schmidt, Kodiak, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0078)
      - Chris Price, Unalaska, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0079)
      - Guy Powell, Kodiak, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0080)
      - Bill Paden, Sitka, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0082)
      - Tony Azuyak, Old Harbor, Kodiak, AK (J. Lund), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0083)
      - Piama Robinson Oleyer, Unalaska (J. Lund), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0084)
      - Piama Robinson Oleyer, Unalaska, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0085)
      - Glenn Ujioka (AK Native), AMCC Board-member, commercial fisher, longshoreman, Cordova, AK (Side A); Paul Seaton, AMCC Board-member, commercial fisher, Homer, AK (Side B), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0086)
      - Mark Thomas, Kodiak, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0087)
      - Walter Tellman, AMCC Board from Unalaska, commercial fisher, AK Native, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0088)
      - Walter Tellman, crab-fishing trip, Unalaska, (1 of 2), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0089)
      - Walter Tellman, crab-fishing trip, Unalaska, (2 of 2), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0090)
      - Walter Tellman, Second Interview, Unalaska, 2, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0091)
      - Bob Storrs, Unalaska, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0092)
      - Bob Storrs, Unalaska (J. Lund), original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0093)
      - Jay Stinson, Kodiak, AK, original standard audio-cassette, undated (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10139-CS-0094)
    - Alternatives Federal Credit Union, Ithaca, New York, 1999-2000; 2
      Thirty-one digital audio tapes documenting the community investment and social change programs led by Alternatives Federal Credit Union.
      - Leni Hochman 4/10/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 April 10 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0035)
      - Carol Chernikoff 04/11/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 April 11 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0028)
      - Leslie Muhlhahn 04/11/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 April 11 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0043)
      - Inger Giuffrida 4/12/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 April 12 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0033)
      - Bill Myers 04/12/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 April 12 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0044)
      - Ed Ryan 04/12/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 April 12 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0045)
      - Barbara Brazill/Don Ruff 05/15/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 15 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0026)
      - Meyer/White 05/15/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 15 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0040)
      - Dennis Montgomery 05/15/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 15 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0042)
      - Alexander/Gerrity 05/16/1999, tape 1, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 16 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0021)
      - Alexander/Gerrity 05/16/1999, tape 2, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 16 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0022)
      - Clementine Dubose/Frances Eastman 05/17/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 17 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0031)
      - Jones/Scott/Cooper 5/17/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 17 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0038)
      - Deidre Silverman 05/18/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 18 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0047)
      - Steve Valloney 05/18/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 18 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0051)
      - Paul Carrubia 05/19/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 19 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0027)
      - Patrice Jennings 5/19/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 19 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0037)
      - Sisay Sisouphone 05/19/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 19 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0048)
      - Rosalind Smith 05/19/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 19 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0049)
      - Anne Steinle 05/19/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 19 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0050)
      - The Barbershop 05/20/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 20 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0024)
      - Daniel Lang 05/20/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 20 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0039)
      - Mark Selden 05/20/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 20 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0046)
      - The Bailor Family 05/21/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 21 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0023)
      - Gloria Molina 05/21/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 21 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0041)
      - Alan Cohen 05/22/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 22 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0029)
      - Ithaca Farmers' Market 05/22/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 22 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0036)
      - Kevin Cuddeback 05/23/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 23 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0030)
      - Jeff Furman 05/24/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 24 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0032)
      - Paul Glover 05/24/1999, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 24 (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0034)
      - Anna Sims Bartel, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0025)
    - Communities in Harmony Advocating for Learning and Kids, San Francisco, CA, 1999-2000; 3
      Seventeen digital audio tapes documenting CHALK's Youthline, a teen-staffed hotline and confidential peer mediation service.
      - CHALK, tape 1, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0052)
      - CHALK, tape 2, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0053)
      - CHALK, tape 3, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0054)
      - CHALK, tape 4, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0055)
      - CHALK, tape 5, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0056)
      - CHALK, tape 6, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0057)
      - CHALK, tape 7, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0058)
      - CHALK, tape 8, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0059)
      - CHALK, tape 9, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0060)
      - CHALK, tape 10, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0061)
      - CHALK, tape 11, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0062)
      - CHALK, tape 12, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0063)
      - CHALK, tape 13, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0064)
      - CHALK, tape 14, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0065)
      - CHALK, tape 15, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0066)
      - CHALK, tape 16, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0067)
      - CHALK, tape 17, original DAT audio-cassette, undated (Box 23, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0068)
    - Dine bi iina, Inc., Navajo Nation, 1999-2000; 4
      Fourteen digital audio tapes created under the supervision of Jack Loeffler, to document the Diné bí' íína', meaning "Navajo lifeways."
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 1, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 09 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0083)
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 2, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 09 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0084)
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 3, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 24 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0085)
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 4, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 25 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0086)
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 5, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 25 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0087)
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 6, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 28 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0088)
      - Jack Loeffler, tape 7, original DAT audio-cassette, 1999 May 28 (Box 24, Audio-cassette RL10139-DAT-0089)